majorleaguelacrosse.com 2007-12-25

# majorleaguelacrosse.com: Privacy Statement

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Major League Lacrosse, LLC is the organization that produces www.majorleaguelacrosse.com, (“Website”). We encourage the interactive nature of online media and strive to educate parents and children about safeguarding their privacy while online. We urge parents to discuss with their children the restrictions regarding releasing personal information on the web and we urge children to check with their parents before entering information on any website. This Privacy Policy is applicable to the Website, [www.majorleaguelacrosse.com](http://www.majorleaguelacrosse.com/) **General** You can visit and enjoy our Website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, we offer some special services, and for these services to work properly we will need you to share with us certain personal information about yourself. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax), and birthdate. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on the applicable page(s) of the Website. **Use and Disclosure of Information** We may use personally identifiable information for such purposes as sending electronic newsletters, conducting contests and sweepstakes, and responding to questions regarding our products and services. We currently do not disclose to third parties personally identifiable information, except as follows: (1) from time to time, we may transfer, disclose or share such information with third parties who may be engaged by us specifically to handle and deliver certain online activities (e.g. conducting contests and sweepstakes). Such third parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes; (2) in the event that all or substantially all of the assets relating to Major League Lacrosse, LLC are transferred or sold to another entity, personally identifiable information submitted to us may be transferred to the acquiring entity; (3) we may disclose personally identifiable information to one or more Major League Lacrosse Teams, to the extent that you've submitted information that relates specifically to that Team (e.g., you've asked to receive the newsletter of one or more Teams via email), so that they may learn more about fans like you, and provide better services to you; (4) on occasion, we may offer a special promotion (such as a sweepstakes, contest or a free subscription to goods and services) on the Website in conjunction with a third party service provider, sponsor or promotional partner, and share your information with that sponsor or promotional partner so that it can send you other special promotions it offers, but only if you give us permission to do so; (5) finally, we may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with law or requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property or safety of our website, users of our website and others. _Information Automatically Collected._ We use automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive) and single-pixel GIF images alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us, to make our Website work better, to understand Website usage and trends, deliver a more personalized experience and to improve our content and offerings. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, without limitation, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; login name and password; type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other customers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, on, and from our Website, including date and time; cookie information; products you viewed or searched for; and your purchase history. We may also use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also use personal information to enable you to use a "shopping cart" if you want to purchase goods or services while on our Website, and to offer you products, programs, or services based on purchase and Website usage behavior that you and/or other customers have exhibited. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to accept or reject cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services on our Website. _Spyware and Adware._ We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with our Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. "Spyware" or "adware" is any software which has been downloaded to and/or installed on an Internet user's computer, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred. _Aggregated Demographic Information._ We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties, but this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Therefore, no personal information is disclosed in this manner. _Disclosure for Legal Purposes._ The law requires that we may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information (see "Cookies" section above for examples of non-personal information) pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use and disclose share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. **How You Can Review Your Personal Information** If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during registration on the Website, and whether you want to receive communications from us, you can call us at 617-746-9980. If you want to close your account with us and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you can call us at 617-746-9980. **Links** Our Website contains links to other sites produced by Major League Lacrosse, LLC and websites operated by unrelated third parties. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information from you. The Privacy Policy applies only to this Website. **Special Rules For Children** Major League Lacrosse, LLC is committed to complying fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. We cannot collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen [13] without the consent of that child's parent. The statements in this Privacy Policy generally about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, with the added protection of the special rules that follow. **Parental Consent** Some services on the Website (e.g., Shop, Ticketing, Auctions) require the submission of a credit card number along with personal information, and are therefore not available to children. Other services on the Website may not be available to children under the age of thirteen. From time to time, we may request limited personally identifiably information (e.g. email address and/ or email address of parent or third party) in order to conduct online contests or sweepstakes or offer other online activities (e.g. electronic post cards, newsletters). We do not condition participation in any of our online activities on the disclosure of more information than what is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. In the event a child under the age of 13 asks to receive our electronic Newsletter or participate in an online contest or sweepstakes, prior to processing the request, we will send an email to the child asking for his/ her parent’s email address. If the child does not reply, his/ her request to participate is not processed and the child’s information is deleted. If we do receive a parent’s email address, we send the child’s parent a notification email informing him/ her of the child’s request to participate in the online activity, and give the option to have his/ her child’s information removed from our database. At any time after receiving this notification email, the child’s parent has the opportunity to exercise the option to request that we remove the child’s information from our database by following the “unsubscribe” instructions found on our website and newsletter, or by calling us at 617-746-9980. All information collected may be transferred, disclosed or shared with third parties who may be engaged by us specifically to handle the execution of the online event (e.g. newsletter, sweepstakes). These third parties may not use it for other purposes and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information. **Contact Us** If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: Major League Lacrosse, LLC Brighton Landing East Suite 125 Boston, MA 02135 Phone: (617) 746-9980 Fax: (617) 746-9988 Or send an e-mail to [info@majorleaguelacrosse.com](mailto:info@majorleaguelacrosse.com%3E%3Cfont%20color=) **Notification of Changes** If we decide to make an important change to our Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on our homepage so that you can review the updated policy. If at any point we wish to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by means of an e-mail and give you the opportunity to indicate whether you consent to the proposed use. **LAST UPDATED AND EFFECTIVE DATE: April 6, 2006**
